<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The International Forum of Artificial Intelligence and STEM Education on IFAISE2020</title>
    <link>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The International Forum of Artificial Intelligence and STEM Education on IFAISE2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Shaanxi Normal University</copyright><atom:link href="https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/call-for-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/call-for-papers/</guid>
      <description>Important deadlines (all is Beijing time):
 Deadline for full paper: January 31, 2021 The deadline for papers has been delayed. Please submit your full paper to the conference mailbox IFAISE2020@163.com before January 31, 2021. Please finish your paper by January 31st,2021. The organizing committees will have a review and select the best paper from the submitted full papers  Requirements for conference proposals/abstracts, papers
  The proposal/abstract should include a title, author name(s), organization, and e-mail address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committees</title>
      <link>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/committees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/committees/</guid>
      <description>International Committees(to be updated)  Yiyu Cai, Associate Professor, Nanyang Technological University, Singapore Eric Hamilton, Professor, Pepperdine University, USA Manabu Sumida, Professor, Secretary-General of Japan Society for Science Education, Asia Regional Representative, International Council of Associations for Science Education (ICASE) (2020-2023), Japan Virgilio U. Manzano, Professor, Dean, Graduate School and Advanced Studies of the Urdaneta City University, Chair of Membership Standing Committee, International Council of Associations for Science Education (ICASE) (2020-2023), Philippines Bulent Cavas, Professor, Dokuz Eylul University, Immediate Past President &amp;amp; Chair of Web Communications Standing Committee, International Council of Associations for Science Education (ICASE) (2020-2023), Turkey Declan Kennedy, Senior Lecturer in Science Education, University College Cork, President-Elect &amp;amp; Chair of World Headquarters Coordinator Standing Committee, International Council of Associations for Science Education (ICASE) (2020-2023), Ireland Steven Sexton, Senior Lecturer in Science Education, University of Otago, Editor of Science Education International Journal &amp;amp; Chair of Pre-secondary &amp;amp; Informal Science Education Standing Committee ,International Council of Associations for Science Education (ICASE) (2020-2023), New Zealand Manuel Filipe Pereira Cunha Martins Costa, Professor, Universidade do Minho, Campus de Gualtar Braga, Europe Regional Representative,, International Council of Associations for Science Education (ICASE) (2020-2023), Portugal Teresa J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/contact-us/</guid>
      <description> Dr. SARFRAZ Aslam :15667033013, E-mail: sarfrazaslam@qq.com Mr. TUO Pan (doctoral student):15686756860, E-mail: tuopan031@126.com Ms. ZHAO Lu,18911490934, luzhao89@casisd.cn Ms. LIU JingJie Liu (Master student):17865329748, E-mail: 1370895697@qq.com Submission and consultation mailbox: IFAISE2020@163.com Advertisement and sponsors please contact: Ms. YU ShuZhen:15901601057, E-mail: yushuzhen0721@163.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invited Speakers</title>
      <link>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/invited-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/invited-speakers/</guid>
      <description>Keynote Speakers .tg img { display: block; } .tg { border-collapse:collapse; border-spacing:0; text-align:center;vertical-align:center } .tg td{ font-size:14px; overflow:hidden; padding:20px; width: 33%; white-space: pre-line } .tg td .name { color:#5B9BD5; font-weight: bold}   Prof. XIONG Zhang  Deputy director of academic committee of Beihang University  Prof. Gwo-Jen Hwang  Taiwan University of Science and Technology  Prof. Eric Hamilton  Pepperdine University    Prof. Yiyu Cai  Nanyang Technological University, Singapore  Associate Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/program/</guid>
      <description>.tg {border-collapse:collapse;border-spacing:0;} .tg td{border-color:black;border-style:solid;border-width:1px;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;font-size:14px; overflow:hidden;padding:10px 5px;word-break:normal;} .tg th{border-color:black;border-style:solid;border-width:1px;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;font-size:14px; font-weight:normal;overflow:hidden;padding:10px 5px;word-break:normal;} .tg .tg-0lax{text-align:center;vertical-align:top}     Time Activity Host     Morning 8:30-8:55 Opening ceremony (Welcome speeches)
(SNNU Vice President Dong Zhibao, China Science Academy’s Center Director Zhou Jianzhong, SNNU SOE Dean Chen Peng) ZHANG BaoHui   8:55-9:00 Photo time --   9:00-9:30 Keynote speech 1 in Chinese (Prof. XIONG Zhang)
Online society and artificial intelligence ZHAO Lu   9:30-10:00 Keynote speech 2 in Chinese (Associate Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/registration/</guid>
      <description>Due to the COVID 19 pandemic, this conference will be conducted purely online. If you are interested in attending the conference, please fill in the registration form. For more detailed information about how to participate, please visit
 the conference websites the WeChat public account of the School of Education, Shaanxi Normal University the website of Prof. Baohui ZHANG: http://zhangbaohui.snnu.edu.cn/ and WeChat public account   IFAISE2020 registration form (Chinese)   IFAISE2020 registration form (English)   User manual for ZOOM system(Chinese)   User manual for ZOOM system(English)    Welcome to join QQ group for this conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report</title>
      <link>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ifaise2020.edtechstar.com/en/report/</guid>
      <description> Shaanxi Normal University News Website College News - The International Forum of Artificial Intelligence and STEM Education (Xi’an, online) was hosted by the School of Education   Shaanxi Normal University School of Education News Website - The School of Education successfully hosted “The International Forum of Artificial Intelligence and STEM Education (Xi’an, online) “   Shaanxi Normal University International Programs Office - New breakthroughs in funding for foreign-related academic activities of our school    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
